Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1962-1986; 7; 15 cubic ft.
  - NYS Democratic Legislative Campaign Committee, Undated (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 91)
  - NYS Democrats, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 92)
  - NYS Federation of Catholic School Parents, 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 93)
  - NYS Governor's Race, 1982 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 94)
  - NYS Political Action Committee, ca. 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 95)
  - Newsletters, 1969; 1975; 1978-1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 96)
  - Niagara County Conservative Party, 1980-1981 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 97)
  - None Dare Call it Treason -- Reviews, 1964 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 98)
  - Northern Ireland, 1982 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 99)
  - Nuclear Energy, 1979-1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 100)
  - Nuclear Weapons, 1966-1967; 1975; 1977-1978; 1982 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 101)
  - Nurses, 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 102)
  - Nursing Homes, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 103)
  - Obscenity, 1964; 1966; 1974-1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 104)
  - Oceans, 1969 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 105)
  - O'Connor, Frank D., 1966-1967 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 106)
  - O'Connor, Robert J., 1970 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 107)
  - O'Doherty, Kieran, 1962; 1968 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 108)
  - Off-Track Betting, 1964; 1972; 1975-1976; 1978-1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 109)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1973 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 110)
  - O'Hair, Madalyn Murray, 1971 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 111)
  - Ohio, 1973-1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Oklahoma, 1974 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Olympics, 1976-1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - O'Neil, Pat, 1972 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Onondaga County, 1980-1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Operation Boomerang, 1971 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Operation Wake Up -- Anti-Equal Rights Amendment, 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Oppenheimer, Dr. Robert, 1963 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Orange County Conservative Party, 1981 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Order of Lafayette, 1966 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Order to Show Cause -- Election Case, 1977 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Organization Manual, ca. 1964 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Organizations, 1971; 1979 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - O'Rourke, Andrew, 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - OSHA (Occupational Safety and Health Administration), 1970-1971; 1976-1979 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Osteopathic Medicine, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Otsego County, 1979 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Ottinger, Richard L., [1980] (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, 1971 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Panama Canal Treaty, 1976-1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Parades, 1967; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Parents & Taxpayers, 1973; 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Parks, 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Patrick Henry Group -- Desegration and Race Relations, ca. 1965 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Pennsylvania Conservative Union, 1977; 1980-1981 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - PERB -- Public Employees Relations Board (NYS), 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Pfister, M/Sgt. Joseph, 1971 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Philadelphia Society, 1965 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Phyllis Schlafly Report, The, 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Planned Parenthood, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Pledge of Allegiance, 1977 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Pledge of Allegiance Assembly Resolution, 1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Plumme's Views, 1965 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Podium Club, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Polar Prison, [1983] (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Police, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Police Files on Non-Criminals, 1976 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Police Memorial Day, 1972-1974 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Police Review Board, ca. 1965 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Polish American Democratic Committee, 1974 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Political Action Committees -- Conservative, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Political Euthanasia, 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Political Report, 1981 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Poll -- Catholic, 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Population Food Fund, 1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Populism, 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Posters -- Campaign, 1977 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - P.P.I. Report (Political Profiles), 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Previte, Joseph J., Esq, 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Price Fixing, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Primaries and Delegates -- Folder 1, 1964-1965 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Primaries and Delegates -- Folder 2, 1965 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Pro Ecclesia Foundation, [ ], 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Public Employees & Right to Strike, 1977 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Public Office - Public Trust, 1974 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Public Service Commission, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Quick Guide to Federal Election Law, 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Rappleyea, C.D. "Rapp", 1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1981-1982; 1984; 1987 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Real Property Taxation -- Assembly Bill, 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Reapportionment Legislation, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Reform -- Government, 1964; 1973 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Regan, Ned, [1980] (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Registering for the Draft R-3, 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Rensselaer County, 1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Resumes, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Richmond County, 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - "Right to Life" Organizations, 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1974-1976 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Rockland County, Undated (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Rocky Mountain Conservative -- Political Action Conference, 1977 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Rutkowski, Edward, 1986-1987 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - St. Patrick's Cocktail Party -- Sponsored by CPNYS, 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Saratoga County, 1977 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Seminerio, Anthony, 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Senate Districts -- 3rd, 1974; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Senate Districts -- 4th, 1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Senate Districts -- 5th, 1980; 1982-1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Senate Districts -- 7th, 1974; 1977; 1979 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Senate Districts -- 9th, 1972; 1976; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Senate Districts -- 10th, 1976-1978; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Senate Districts -- 11th, 1974; 1976; 1979; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - Senate Districts -- 12th, 1976-1977; 1980; 1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - Senate Districts -- 13th, 1972; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - Senate Districts -- 14th, 1974; 1976; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - Senate Districts -- 18th, 1976 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 87)
  - Senate Districts -- 21st, 1977-1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 88)
  - Senate Districts -- 25th, 1980; 1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 89)
  - Senate Districts -- 26th, 1972; 1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 90)
  - Senate Districts -- 29th, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 91)
  - Senate Districts -- 34th, 1976-1978; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 92)
  - Senate Districts -- 35th, 1977; 1979 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 93)
  - Senate Districts -- 36th, 1972; 1975; 1977-1978; 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 94)
  - Senate Districts -- 37th, 1978; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 95)
  - Senate Districts -- 38th, 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 96)
  - Senate Districts -- 39th, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 97)
  - Senate Districts -- 40th, 1976; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 98)
  - Senate Districts -- 41st, 1976; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 99)
  - Senate Districts -- 42nd, 1976 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 100)
  - Senate Districts -- 43rd, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 101)
  - Senate Districts -- 44th, 1976; 1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 102)
  - Senate Districts -- 46th, 1976 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 103)
  - Senate Districts -- 48th, ca. 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 104)
  - Senate Districts -- 49th, 1976 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 105)
  - Senate Districts -- 51st, 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 106)
  - Senate Districts -- 52nd, 1975-1976; 1978; 1980; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 107)
  - Senate Districts -- 53rd, 1974; 1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 108)
  - Senate Districts -- 55th, 1979 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 109)
  - Senate Districts -- 58th, 1975 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 110)
  - Senate Districts -- 59th, 1974; 1977; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 111)
  - Senate Districts -- 60th, 1978; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 112)
  - Socialist Labor Party, 1973-1974 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 113)
  - Solomon, Con. Jerry, 1983 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 114)
  - Star Wars -- S.D.I., 1980 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 115)
  - State of Long Island, 1986 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 116)
  - Student Loans, 1978 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 117)
  - Suffolk County, 1974; 1977; 1979-1980; 1982 (Box 14 (7-Subject Files), Folder 118)
  - Suffolk County, 1983 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Sullivan County, 1982 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Symms, Sen. Steve, 1982 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Tax Indexing, 1979 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Taylor Law -- (Illegal Public Employee Strikes) -- editorial, 1980 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Today in France, 1977 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Transportation, 1974-1978 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Trib, The, 1977 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Turkey, 1983 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Twenty-one Year Old Drinking Age, 1983-1984 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F., 1962-1963; 1965; 1979-1980 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - United Nations, 1962-1966; 1970-1971; 1975; 1978 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - United States Decline, 1979 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - U.S. Senate Ratings by Conservative Organizations, 1980 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - U.S. Supreme Court -- "Catalytic Courts", 1974 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - United States Youth Council, 1983 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Velella, Guy, 1981 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Vietnam -- Ad Hoc Committee Against United States Recognition of Communist Vietnam, 1977 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Veterans of America, ca. 1985 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - VIVA (Voice for Innocent Victims of Abortion), 1980 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Voter Views, 1987 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Voting -- Reapportionment of Districts in NYS, 1982 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Washington Legal Foundation, 1982; 1987 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Welfare, 1983-1984 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Westchester County, 1965; 1975 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Wortley, George, 1983; 1985 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Wyoming County, 1979 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Youth Education for Citizenship, 1972-1973 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF), 1973-1979; 3 folders (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29-31)
  - YAF -- Folder 4, 1961-1971 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - YAF -- Folder 5, 1972-1974 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - YAF -- Folder 6, 1975-1981 (Box 15 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
- Clippings File, 1962-1987; 8; 12 cubic ft.
  This series contains clippings from newspapers, magazines, etc. on social, political and economic issues (foreign, domestic, state, and city), candidates and campaigns, and people in the news.
  - Abzug, Bella, 1974-1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - ADA (Americans for Democratic Action), 1964 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - Adirondack Park, 1972-1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - Adoption, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - Afghanistan, 1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - Africa, 1974-1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - Aged, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - Agnew, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - Aid to Non-public Schools, 1974; 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - Aid to North Vietnam, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - Airline Deregulation, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - Airlines, 1977; 1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - Alaska, 1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - Alcoholism, 1964; 1975; 1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - Alexander, Lee, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - Aliens, 1974-1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 17)
  - Allegheny County, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - Allen, Robert S., 1972 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - Amendment (First), 1977-1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - America, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - American Airlines, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - American Conservative Union, 1974; 1978-1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - American Medical Association, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - American Party, 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - Amnesty, 1971-1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - Amtrak, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - Anderson, Jack, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - Anderson, John, 1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - Angola, 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - Anti-crime Plan, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - Anti-poverty Programs, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - Antitrust, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - Arizona, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - Armed Forces, 1973; 1976; 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - Arson, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - Ashbrook, John, 1971-1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - Asia, 1975; 1977-1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - Assessment (100%), 1977; 1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - Atheists, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - Atlantic Convention Bill, 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43)
  - Attica, 1971; 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 44)
  - Attorney General -- NYS, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 45)
  - Attorney General -- NYS, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - Australia, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - Authorities, 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - Auxiliary Police, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - B-1 Bomber, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - Badillo, Herman, 1973; 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - Bail, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - Baker, Howard, 1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - Bakke Case, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - Balogh, Sandor, Undated (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - Banks, 1971; 1973; 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - Barclay, Douglas, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - Battista, Vito P., 1969-1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - Bauman, Robert, 1973; 1975-1976; 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - Bayh, Birch, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - Beame, Abraham, 1973-1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - Beame -- Staff, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - "Beaver", The, 1975; 1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 63)
  - Beckman, John, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 64)
  - Bell, Griffin, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 65)
  - Bell, Jeffrey, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 66)
  - Bellamy, Carol, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 67)
  - Biaggi, Mario, 1971-1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68)
  - Biaggi, Mario, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 69)
  - Bicentennial, 1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 70)
  - Bikes, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 71)
  - Bilderberg, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 72)
  - Bilingual Education, 1976; 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 73)
  - Blackout, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 74)
  - Blacks, 1971-1980 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 75)
  - "Block Busting", 1976; 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 76)
  - Bloom, Jeremiah, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 77)
  - Blumenthal, Al, 1973-1976 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 78)
  - Board of Education, 1972-1974; 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 79)
  - Board of Election -- NYC, 1971-1974; 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 80)
  - Board of Estimate, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 81)
  - Board of Regents, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 82)
  - Bond Issue, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 83)
  - Bond Issue, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 84)
  - Bond Issue, 1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 85)
  - Bork, Robert H., 1987 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 86)
  - Boro President (Manhattan), 1977 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 87)
  - Brasco, Frank, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 88)
  - Bridges, 1979 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 89)
  - Britain, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 90)
  - Broadcasting, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 91)
  - Brooke, Edward, 1976; 1978 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 92)
  - Brooklyn Supreme Court, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Clippings File), Folder 93)
  - Brown, Jerry, 1975-1981 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - Bryant, Anita, 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - Brydges, Earl, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - Buchanan, Pat, 1973; 1975 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - Bucher, Lloyd, 1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - Buckley, Aloise, 1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L. (1972), 01/01/1972-03/31/1972 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L., 04/01/1972-06/30/1972 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L., 07/1972-03/1973 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L., 04/1973-12/1973 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L., 01/1974 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L. -- Nix on Nixon, 1974 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L., 1975 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L. -- Campaign '76, 1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - Buckley, Sen. J.L., 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16)
  - Buckley, James L., 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 17)
  - Buckley, William, 1968-1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - Bullard, David, 1974 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - Bureaucracy -- Federal, 1972-1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - Bureaucracy, 1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - Bureaucracy -- New York, 1971; 1977; 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - Burden, Carter, 1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - Burnstein, Sen. Karen, 1975 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - Bush, George, 1978-1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - Business, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - Business Tax, 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - Busing, 1975-1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - Butz, Earl, 1974 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - Byrd Amendment, 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - Cable TV, 1972-1975 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - Calandra, Sen. John, 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - Califano, Joseph, Undated (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - Cambodia, 1971; 1973; 1978-1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - Campaign, 1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - Campaign, 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - Campaign, 1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - Campaign Contribution, 1966-1967; 1972-1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - Campaign Issues, 1972 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - Campaign Financing, 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - Campaign Material, 1976-1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - Campaign Practices, 1978; 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - Candidates, 1972 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43)
  - Candidates, 1973 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 44)
  - Candidates, 1974 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 45)
  - Caplan vs. Roth, Undated (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - Captive Nations, 1973 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - Caputo, Bruce, 1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - Carlino, Joseph, 1964 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - Carney, William, 1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - Casey, William J., 1980-1981 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - CCOs (Corporate Chiefs Organization), 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - Census, 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - Central America, Undated (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - China, 1965-1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - CIA, 1976-1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - Con Ed, 1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - Congress of the United States -- House of Representatives, 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - Congress (General), 1975-1978 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58A)
  - Connally, 1979 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - Constitution, 1987 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - Constitutional Convention Ballot Question, 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - Corporate Boards, 1980 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - CPAC (Conservative Political Action Conference), 1977 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 63)
  - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey (CPES), 1974-1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 64)
  - CPES, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (8-Clippings File), Folder 65)